

### **CONTACT**



**Jesús Acosta** 



+420 770 650 246



kontakt@jesusacosta.cz



Kubištova 1099/2 140 00 Praha 4, Podolí **Czech Republic** 

#### **LANGUAGES**

**SPANISH ENGLISH CZECH** 

\_\_\_\_ C2 **A2** A1

### **SKILLS**

HTML/HTML5 **CSS SQL-Transac** Asp.Net C# Delphi

**PHP** 

Java **JavaScript FoxPro Visual Foxpro** 

Virtualization **Database** 

Inkscape Gimp **PhotoShop** 

Illustrator **CorelDraw OS Windows** 

**OS Linux Support Docker** 

# JESÚS ACOSTA

**Developer / Programmer** Web design

# **PROFILE**

I am University Technician in Computing, I work with these programming languages: PHP, Html, Css, Javascript, C# and Sql-Transac.

I also have worked with Asp.Net, Java, Delphi, FoxPro and Visual FoxPro.

I have worked with database engines (MySQL / SQL Server), Docker and Virtualization (VirtualBox / VMWare) in servers and desktops.

I have also worked with networks and structured cabling. I have had the opportunity to work with office applications (such as Word, Excel, PowerPoint, among others ...) and graphic design applications (such as Inkscape, Gimp, PhotoShop and CorelDraw).

### **EDUCATION**

1989 - 1995

University Institute "Antonio José de Sucre", Valencia, Venezuela. **Higher University Technician in Computer Science.** 

# **EXPERIENCE**

#### 1998 - 2015 SYSTEMS PROGRAMMING ANALYST. University of Carabobo, Valencia, Venezuela.

As part of a team, I participated in the development of software projects, supervised the development of applications according to specifications. Tested, evaluated and recommended ready-made software. Followed up the implemented solutions and made any necessary corrections. Designed and installed network schemes. Designed databases and defined and implemented roles and access levels to them.

#### 1990 - 1998 PROGRAMMER I.

#### University of Carabobo, Valencia, Venezuela.

Worked on Windows and Unix environments. Designed and implemented applications and systems. Coordinate the work plan, together with the supervisor. Prepared periodic reports of the activities. Maintenance and repair of computer equipment.